gladinet.com 2019-12-14

# GLADINET - Privacy Statement

Last modified: May 23, 2018 

At Gladinet we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Gladinet Inc. or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, Gladinet's "services"). 

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website. 

## Information we collect and how we use it

We offer a number of software and services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, such as Gladinet Cloud Desktop Starter Edition or Professional Edition. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information: 

_Information you provide_ \- When you sign up for a Gladinet Account or other Gladinet service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For paid services, such as our premium subscription, we also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers or send directly to our payment processor. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Gladinet services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information. 

_Gladinet cookies_ \- When you visit Gladinet company website and product web site, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Gladinet features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

_Log information_ \- When you use Gladinet services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

_User communications_ \- When you send email or other communication to Gladinet, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

_Affiliated sites_ \- We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Gladinet in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 

Gladinet processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our business partners. 

## Choices for personal information

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Gladinet may not be able to provide those services to you. 

## Right to erasure

If you need to erase your personal data, please contact support@gladinet.com. 

## Information sharing

Gladinet only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Gladinet in the following limited circumstances: 

We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 

We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Gladinet, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

If Gladinet becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Please contact us at privacy@gladinet.com for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data. 

## Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to Gladinet employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

For highly sensitive personal information such as password, Gladinet takes very good measure to protect. As a matter of fact, The original form of password is never stored on Gladinet servers. Only crypto derived form of password is stored, which is good enough to authenticate the user who has the correct password but not enough to retrieve it for you if you forget your password. Gladinet can only reset the password for users who forget. For Single Sign On to work, Gladinet will need to collect and store user credentials. It is encrypted before it is stored. 

If you are using premium services offered by Gladinet, Gladinet needs to collect credit card and related payment information. Payment related information is also highly sensitive. Gladinet takes very good measure to protect. The payment related information is never stored as clear text in Gladinet server. Only encrypted information is stored. 

## Data integrity

Gladinet processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

## Accessing and updating personal information

When you use Gladinet services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users' personal information. We provide the details for these procedures in the specific privacy notices or FAQs for these services. 

## Changes to this policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. 

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site or at privacy@gladinet.com.
